<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pregnancy</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="add_note">Add Note</string>

    <string name="due_date">Due date set up</string>
    <string name="due_date2">Due date</string>

    <string name="due_date_title">Set up due date or the last date of your first period</string>

    <string name="greetings1">Congratulations!You are </string>
    <string name="greetings2">weeks pregnant</string>


    <!--
    //pregnancy
    -->

    <string name="first_week">1 week \n 1st trimester \n 273 days left</string>
    <string name="second_week">2 weeks,6 days \n 1st trimester \n 260 days left</string>
    <string name="third_week">3 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 259 days left</string>
    <string name="fourth_week">4 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 252 days left</string>
    <string name="fifth_week">5 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 245 days left</string>
    <string name="sixth_week">6 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 238 days left</string>
    <string name="seventh_week">7 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 231 days left</string>
    <string name="eight_week">8 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 224 days left</string>
    <string name="nineth_week">9 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 217 days left</string>
    <string name="ten_week">10 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 210 days left</string>
    <string name="eleven_week">11 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 203 days left</string>
    <string name="twelve_week">12 weeks \n 1st trimester \n 196 days left</string>
    <string name="thirteen_week">13 weeks,6 days \n 1st trimester \n 189 days left</string>
    <string name="fourteen_week">14 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 182 days left</string>
    <string name="fifteen_week">15 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 175 days left</string>
    <string name="sixteen_week">16 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 168 days left</string>
    <string name="seventeen_week">17 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 161 days left</string>
    <string name="eighteen_week">18 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 154 days left</string>
    <string name="nineteen_week">19 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 147 days left</string>
    <string name="twenty_week">20 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 140 days left</string>
    <string name="twentyone_week">21 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 133 days left</string>
    <string name="twentytwo_week">22 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 126 days left</string>
    <string name="twentythree_week">23 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 119 days left</string>
    <string name="twentyfour_week">24 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 112 days left</string>
    <string name="twentyfive_week">25 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 105 days left</string>
    <string name="twentysix_week">26 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 98 days left</string>
    <string name="twentyseven_week">27 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 91 days left</string>
    <string name="twentyeight_week">28 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 84 days left</string>
    <string name="twentynine_week">29 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 77 days left</string>
    <string name="thirty_week">30 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 203 70 left</string>
    <string name="thirtyone_week">31 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 63 days left</string>
    <string name="thirtytwo_week">32 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 56 days left</string>
    <string name="thirtythree_week">33 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 49 days left</string>
    <string name="thirtyfour_week">34 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 42 days left</string>
    <string name="thirtyfive_week">35 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 35 days left</string>
    <string name="thirtysix_week">36 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 28 days left</string>
    <string name="thirtyseven_week">37 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 21 days left</string>
    <string name="thirtyeight_week">38 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 14 days left</string>
    <string name="thirtynine_week">39 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n 7 days left</string>
    <string name="fourty_week">40 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n a few days left</string>
    <string name="fourtyone_week">41 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n a few days left</string>
    <string name="fourtytwo_week">42 weeks \n 3rd trimester \n a few days left</string>


    <!--//length-->


    <string name="week_1">-</string>
    <string name="week_2">-</string>
    <string name="week_3">-</string>
    <string name="week_4">-</string>
    <string name="week_5">0.12 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_6">0.2 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_7">0.47 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_8">0.63 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_9">0.91 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_10">1.22 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_11">1.61 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_12">2.13 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_13">2.91 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_14">3.43 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_15">3.98 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_16"> 4.57 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_17">5.12 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_18">5.59 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_19">6.02 in from crown to rump</string>
    <string name="week_20">10.08 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_21">10.51 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_22">10.94 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_23">11.34 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_24">11.81 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_25">13.62 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_26">14.02 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_27">14.41 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_28">14.76 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_29">15.2 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_30">15.71 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_31">16.18 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_32">16.69 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_33">17.24 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_34">17.72 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_35">18.23 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_36">18.66 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_37">19.09 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_38">19.61 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_39">19.92 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_40">20.16 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_41">20.35 in from head to toe</string>
    <string name="week_42">20.71 in from head to toe</string>


    <!--//weight-->

    <string name="week_1oz">-</string>
    <string name="week_2oz">-</string>
    <string name="week_3oz">-</string>
    <string name="week_4oz">-</string>
    <string name="week_5oz">-</string>
    <string name="week_6oz">-</string>
    <string name="week_7oz">0.02-0.04 oz</string>
    <string name="week_8oz">0.04-0.05 oz</string>
    <string name="week_9oz">0.07 oz</string>
    <string name="week_10oz">0.14 oz</string>
    <string name="week_11oz">0.25-0.28 oz</string>
    <string name="week_12oz">0.49 oz</string>
    <string name="week_13oz">0.81-0.85 oz</string>
    <string name="week_14oz">1.48-1.55 oz</string>
    <string name="week_15oz">2.47 oz</string>
    <string name="week_16oz"> 3.53 oz</string>
    <string name="week_17oz">4.87-5.01 oz</string>
    <string name="week_18oz">6.7 oz</string>
    <string name="week_19oz">8.47 oz</string>
    <string name="week_20oz">10.58 oz</string>
    <string name="week_21oz">12.7 oz</string>
    <string name="week_22oz">15.17 oz</string>
    <string name="week_23oz">1.1 lb</string>
    <string name="week_24oz">1.32 lb</string>
    <string name="week_25oz">1.46-1.48 lb</string>
    <string name="week_26oz">1.68 lb</string>
    <string name="week_27oz">1.92-1.94 lb</string>
    <string name="week_28oz">2.2-2.43 lb</string>
    <string name="week_29oz">2.54 lb</string>
    <string name="week_30oz">2.87-2.91 lb</string>
    <string name="week_31oz">3.31 lb</string>
    <string name="week_32oz">3.75 lb</string>
    <string name="week_33oz">4.10-4.41 lb</string>
    <string name="week_34oz">4.74 lb</string>
    <string name="week_35oz">5.25-5.29 lb</string>
    <string name="week_36oz">5.73 lb</string>
    <string name="week_37oz">6.28-6.39 lb</string>
    <string name="week_38oz">6.61-6.83 lb</string>
    <string name="week_39oz">7.05-7.28 lb</string>
    <string name="week_40oz">7.5-7.72 lb</string>
    <string name="week_41oz">7.93 lb</string>
    <string name="week_42oz">8.12 lb</string>


    <!-- //size of-->


    <string name="week_1size">-</string>
    <string name="week_2size">-</string>
    <string name="week_3size">-</string>
    <string name="week_4size">poppy seed</string>
    <string name="week_5size">seesame seed</string>
    <string name="week_6size">pomegranate seed</string>
    <string name="week_7size">blueberry</string>
    <string name="week_8size">raspberry</string>
    <string name="week_9size">cherry</string>
    <string name="week_10size">green olive</string>
    <string name="week_11size">fig</string>
    <string name="week_12size">lime</string>
    <string name="week_13size">peach</string>
    <string name="week_14size">nectarine</string>
    <string name="week_15size">apple</string>
    <string name="week_16size"> avocado</string>
    <string name="week_17size">pear</string>
    <string name="week_18size">bell pepper</string>
    <string name="week_19size">pomegranate</string>
    <string name="week_20size">ear of corn</string>
    <string name="week_21size">grapefruit</string>
    <string name="week_22size">zucchini</string>
    <string name="week_23size">large mango</string>
    <string name="week_24size">papaya</string>
    <string name="week_25size">pomelo</string>
    <string name="week_26size">eggplant</string>
    <string name="week_27size">cauliflower</string>
    <string name="week_28size">Kabocha squash</string>
    <string name="week_29size">butternut squash</string>
    <string name="week_30size">bunch of bananas</string>
    <string name="week_31size">coconut</string>
    <string name="week_32size">large cabbage</string>
    <string name="week_33size">pineapple</string>
    <string name="week_34size">cantaloupe</string>
    <string name="week_35size">honeydew melon</string>
    <string name="week_36size">bunch of grapes</string>
    <string name="week_37size">swiss chard</string>
    <string name="week_38size">leek</string>
    <string name="week_39size">small pumpkin</string>
    <string name="week_40size">watermelon</string>
    <string name="week_41size">big watermelon</string>

    <string name="week_42size">big watermelon</string>


    <!--
    //pregnant women string-->

    <string name="first_week_p">For most women, especially for those who aren’t planning a pregnancy, week one goes by without them realizing they are pregnant. Even week 2 may go undetected. Lots of women’s monthly cycles are variable, so most women assume that when their monthly menstrual cycle is late, it’s just that — late.\n There aren’t any immediate, obvious pregnancy symptoms during the first week, but there are signs such as fatigue, loss of interest in things, mood swings, and the constant need to urinate. However, most women attribute these symptoms to PMS, rather than assuming they are pregnant.\n  The menstrual cycle lasts for approximately 28 days, although it can be as short as 24 days or as long as 35.
It begins when an egg leaves the ovary and travels into the fallopian tubes, where it’s met by sperm and fertilized. From there the fertilized egg travels through the fallopian tubes and into the uterus, where implantation occurs. \n Some people speculate a woman isn’t really pregnant during the first week of pregnancy, since fertilization takes place during the second week. This is the main reason why so many pregnancies go undetected during the first week.</string>
    <string name="second_week_p">The first two weeks of pregnancy can be very exciting for a woman … and yet not so exciting. The not-so-exciting part of this second week is that the ever-so-popular pregnancy symptoms begin to kick in.\n Tender breasts, nausea, dizziness, and drowsiness are just some of the symptoms women face during the second week.</string>
    <string name="third_week_p">Despite their symptoms, many women are still unsure whether they’re actually pregnant during the third week, so they either take over-the-counter pregnancy tests or visit their OB/GYN.
If you’re unsure whether you’re pregnant, you should contact your OB/GYN to confirm at this point. After confirmation of an existing pregnancy, an obstetrician should be selected to keep in contact with over the next nine months.\n If you don’t have one, or you’re unsure about selecting a good obstetrician, you can ask your family or friends for a recommendation. Once you’ve made an appointment with your obstetrician, make a list of questions for the first visit.
Your questions should include how often visits should take place, necessary changes that need to be made to diet and lifestyle, what vitamins you should take, and whether any medications you may be taking need to be reviewed.
If this is your first pregnancy, your thoughts and emotions will be racing, so be sure not to forget to ask about something that is important to you.</string>
    <string name="fourth_week_p">If you’re still not sure whether or not you’re pregnant, now would be a great time to confirm. At this point there should be signs, such as missed menstrual periods, hormonal changes, and nausea and vomiting. Contacting an OB/GYN or taking over-the-counter pregnancy tests are both great ways of finding out the truth.\n If you have confirmed that you are pregnant, changes in diet and lifestyle are critical during the fourth week. After all, it’s the fourth week — you’ve been pregnant for one whole month. The first trimester is underway, and this is a very critical point in your baby’s development.\n Fetuses are at high risk for abnormalities during this stage, as the baby’s brain, heart, head, spinal cord, bones, muscles, tissues, and teeth are all developing. If you’ve been taking in toxins such as alcohol, it’s very important to stop those habits to increase your baby’s chances of remaining healthy.</string>
    <string name="fifth_week_p">By week 5 in your pregnancy, there’s no denying it as a whole month has passed. You’re passing all at-home pregnancy tests, you’ve missed your period, and you’ve begun to experience the pregnancy symptoms – breast tenderness, fatigue, and nausea or morning sickness. It’s an important part of the pregnancy. In the 5th week, ultrasounds will begin to show conclusively that there’s a baby in there.\n So you’re experiencing all the pregnancy symptoms, and the pregnancy tests show that HCG levels in your body are high enough to confirm that you are pregnant. But with the higher hormone levels come feelings that are raging out of control.\n You’re not quite showing yet, but you feel bloated. Your abdomen won’t begin rising until about 14 weeks, but the pressure will increase and make you feel like you need to use the restroom more often. Most people won’t be able to tell by looking at you that you’re pregnant, but you’ll know.</string>
    <string name="sixth_week_p">Reaching the sixth week of pregnancy is a milestone. It marks the halfway point through the first trimester. The baby is definitely growing, changing, and developing, and at six weeks, the shape is really starting to come into focus. An expectant mother can be 100 percent sure she is pregnant by the sixth week, as pregnancy symptoms are in full swing, and all tests are returning positive results.\n As the baby develops, you will begin to show, and you will feel symptoms of being pregnant, including mood swings, intense food cravings, morning sickness, fatigue, weight gain, tender breasts, and nausea.\n These pregnancy symptoms are due to the fast rate at which your baby is growing, but there are a few things you can do to ease the pains. Many women gain about five pounds during the first trimester, but many others lose weight during the first six weeks of pregnancy due to the nausea and morning sickness.\n There’s no need for worry, either way. All women are different and have different experiences with their weight during pregnancy.\n Most women schedule their first doctor check-up in the sixth week. Expectant moms will get their first ultrasounds done to make sure that everything is all right with both mom and baby, and to get their first glimpse of the developing embryo.</string>
    <string name="seventh_week_p">Seven weeks into your pregnancy, a lot of things are happening with you and your baby. You’re midway through your first trimester and everything is moving quite quickly. If you haven’t looked into getting an OB/GYN, now is probably a good time to do so, as critical tests and check-ups will be necessary from now until the birth of your baby.\n Although you’re probably not showing much at this stage, you are more than likely feeling very pregnant and bloated. Some women begin to show a small swelling in their lower abdomen; in most cases the baby is too small to be causing this, and it’s more than likely due to the bloating.\n You may find yourself craving foods that you once thought were disgusting. This is normal, and as long as it’s healthy for your baby, it’s okay to indulge. One of the major changes that occurs in your body during the seventh week is the development of your mucous plug.
Your cervix is forming a plug in the opening of the cervical canal to seal off the uterus for protection. You’ll eventually lose this plug when labor and childbirth are close.</string>
    <string name="eight_week_p">Many things are happening during the eighth week of pregnancy. Although many women schedule their first doctor appointments during the sixth and seventh weeks, many practitioners prefer to wait until after the eighth week, or two missed periods, before scheduling an appointment.
The first doctor appointment tends to take a little longer than the rest, as you and your doctor are filling out lots of paperwork, you are answering lots of questions, etc. You also get your first ultrasound done, so you will see your baby for the first time., so you will see your baby for the first time.\n The ultrasound will also tell you how many heartbeats are there — you may have twins! This is also the stage at which you begin all the paperwork required by the government to officially record your baby with the registrar.
This will get your baby a birth certificate after the birth. You are more than halfway through the first trimester, so get ready!</string>
    <string name="nineth_week_p">During the ninth week of pregnancy, you and your baby are going through many changes very rapidly. If you haven’t already, you may be preparing for your first prenatal visit with your health care provider. To make things easier for your doctor, you may want to write down some things about yourself, including medications, exercise habits, eating habits, and medical history.\n You may be noticing weight gain, but it’s likely more due to water retention than the baby. Many women experience severe mood swings and other pregnancy symptoms during this week, but again, this is due to the hormones (especially progesterone) in your system.\n Some of the pregnancy symptoms that are still present — such as aches and pains, bloating, and fatigue — will last throughout your pregnancy.</string>
    <string name="ten_week_p">As you go through your tenth week of pregnancy, it’s important to know that your baby is completely out of the embryonic stage and fully into the fetal stage. The best news about the tenth week is that there is less risk for congenital abnormalities. You and your baby are not fully in the clear when it comes to avoiding abnormalities or deformities, but the most critical weeks of development are over. With continued care and medical attention, you are well on your way to having a healthy baby.\n You’ve gained one to three pounds, yet you feel like you’ve gained much more. The bloated feeling hasn’t gone away yet, but as you reach the end of your first trimester, other pregnancy symptoms such as morning sickness are subsiding.\n Hopefully during the tenth week you are feeling much more positive about your pregnancy, since your first check-up has come and gone and you have been able to hear your baby’s heartbeat.
This moment can be very exciting for future parents, and that can offset the negative emotions brought on by the heightened levels of estrogen and progesterone within your body. Hang in there!</string>
    <string name="eleven_week_p">During the eleventh week of pregnancy, many changes are occurring with Mom and baby. Mom has probably heard the baby’s heartbeat by this week, and some of her pregnancy symptoms, such as morning sickness, are dissipating. Mom may even feel well enough to enjoy a night out on the town (without alcohol or cigarettes, of course)</string>
    <string name="twelve_week_p">Week 12 is a significant week in a woman’s pregnancy. It signifies the end of the first trimester and the end of the most critical stage of your baby’s growth and development. After three months pregnant, many women feel more secure in spreading the good news of the pregnancy, and the chances of miscarriage decrease at this point, as long as Mom continues to stay healthy, eat right, exercise accordingly, and follow all doctor’s orders.
</string>
    <string name="thirteen_week_p">You’ve made it through your first trimester, and now, at thirteen weeks along, you’ve entered your second trimester! You’ve still got a long way to go, but the worst of it should be over as long as you stay healthy, continue to eat right, and exercise accordingly.\n You may also begin to experience round ligament pain as the ligaments that support your uterus stretch and pull.\n This pain can be severe, and it may cause you to think that you need to seek medical attention. While this pain is common and normal, you should always call your healthcare provider if you have questions.\n If these pains are accompanied by blood leakage or any other type of fluid loss, you should definitely make an appointment with your healthcare provider immediately, as this could be a sign of something much more serious, such as miscarriage.You may still be experiencing heartburn in the chest and throat. Your breasts are still growing and are probably extremely sensitive due to the colostrum they are producing. Your breasts are preparing for lactation and the mammary ducts are growing larger. Hang in there, Mom!</string>
    <string name="fourteen_week_p">During the fourteenth week of pregnancy you may feel like you can finally relax, since your body has pretty much adjusted to the internal changes that have been happening. You have entered the second week of your second trimester, and although the critical stages of your baby’s development have come and gone, it’s still extremely important that you watch what you eat.\n Be careful, as at this point your appetite will increase and you’ll feel the need to “eat for two.” Your spots and freckles will continue to darken and your breasts will continue to be sensitive, possibly growing in size as you prepare for lactation.\n You may find new moles on your body, but this is normal. Mood swings tend to increase during the second trimester, but talking with a support group, your partner, or your healthcare provider can help with this problem.</string>
    <string name="fifteen_week_p">During the fifteenth week of pregnancy and throughout the second trimester, most women tend to relax a bit more. Most of the worst pregnancy symptoms, like nausea, morning sickness, and fatigue, are decreasing more and more as the days go by. The pain that comes at the end of the pregnancy is far off, so you can finally sit back and enjoy the fact that you are pregnant.\n As mentioned before, the fifteenth week does not herald significant changes within your body. Many women have gained up to five pounds by this week, although weight gain varies from mom to mom.\n It is quite natural if you have gained a little more or a little less than that. The toughest situation moms-to-be face during this week is that the ligaments that support the uterus are continuing to grow, causing sharp pain in the abdomen.</string>
    <string name="sixteen_week_p">During the second trimester there are many tests you should have done to ensure that everything is going well and that your baby isn’t showing signs of certain chromosomal abnormalities. To learn more about these tests, visit our Prenatal Testing article.\n The biggest change you will notice in your body at 16 weeks is the look and size of your breasts. Milk glands start production and veins become more visible as the blood flow increases.\n You may be feeling an increased weight in your womb as your waistline continues to stretch and expand. Pregnancy back pains are also due to begin, as most women gain five to ten pounds at this point.
Hang in there, Mommy!</string>
    <string name="seventeen_week_p">As week 17 comes and goes, you are probably feeling much more comfortable with your pregnancy and dealing more easily with your symptoms. You are starting to show, and you look more like a pregnant woman than a woman who is overeating.\n At 17 weeks you will begin to show. Your abdomen grows as your internal organs move around, providing space for the uterus and baby. Your uterus begins pushing your intestines up and outwards, towards the sides of your abdomen, allowing you to feel your uterus more when you’re standing rather than sleeping or lying down.\n There may be an occasional pain in the legs called sciatic nerve pain, which can be excruciating for some women. The sciatic nerve is the largest nerve in the body and it runs under the uterus, traveling down the entire length of the leg.\n The cause of the pain is usually pressure on the nerve caused by the growing baby, and it can sometimes be alleviated by avoiding standing in one place for too long, or by putting pillows under your legs while sleeping at night to provide support.\n Your doctor may be able to suggest other ways to relieve the pain. Sweating may increase as the blood volume increases.\n Also, some women experience vaginal discharge and/or nasal congestion. This is normal and goes away after child birth.
</string>
    <string name="eighteen_week_p">During the eighteenth week of pregnancy, some women experience an increase in appetite. Make sure that you try to eat healthy foods that are high in fiber.\n The most important thing right now is your baby, and everything you put into your mouth affects your baby’s development.\n Your waistline is probably expanding greatly during this week. If you take two fingers and place them just below your belly, you can feel your uterus.\n It’s still the size of a cantaloupe, and at this point you’re starting to show. Some women have gained up to thirteen pounds by the eighteenth week, but every mom-to-be is different.\n If you’ve gained more or less, talk with your doctor to make sure you are on a healthy track.
You may notice increasingly frequent trips to the restroom, so you may want to make it a habit to use the restroom before you lie down or get comfortable.\n Some women may experience a dizzy or light-headed feeling during this stage in their pregnancy. You can minimize this dizziness by changing positions while standing or sitting, and by not moving too quickly.</string>
    <string name="nineteen_week_p">The nineteenth week of pregnancy is a very important week for both Mom and baby. There are many critical changes happening within both systems. As the middle of the pregnancy term approaches, Mom is probably feeling more comfortable with her pregnancy and the changes in her body.
As you go through your nineteenth week of pregnancy, you may notice more changes on the exterior of your body. Dry, flaky skin may form as your metabolism and blood volume increase.\n Your tendency to dehydrate and your sensitivity to heat will increase, so it’s important that you continue to provide your body with plenty of fluids; water is best. Stay away from caffeine as much as possible.
Caffeine raises blood pressure and increases your heart rate, and it may also affect the baby. Sodas, fruit juices, and sugary beverages may be dehydrating rather than hydrating. Avoid artificial sweeteners too.\n Try to keep your skin lubricated with lotion as much as possible. This can help to prevent skin problems.\n Cocoa butter is good for preventing stretch marks, and a good pregnancy diet can help to reduce problems with skin as well.
</string>
    <string name="twenty_week_p">Week 20 of your pregnancy signifies the middle of your second trimester, as well as the middle of your pregnancy. Congratulations—you’ve survived the fatigue, morning sickness, nausea and other pregnancy symptoms so far.
You are probably starting to feel better at this point, but you may still experience some fatigue and pain. During this week there are many exciting developmental changes happening with your baby.\n Most women who have smaller body frames begin to experience trouble breathing at this point. The baby’s growth has reached the point at which the baby is pressing on your internal organs, making it hard to breathe.
The top of your uterus is parallel with your belly button, and you’ve probably gained close to fifteen pounds.
From this week on, you can expect to gain up to a pound per week. Your waistline continues to expand, and indigestion, heartburn, itching, and constipation probably occur more frequently.\n You’re also experiencing more and more trips to the restroom at this point.\n You need to continue to incorporate plenty of iron into your diet, as your baby is using much of the iron that you take in. Dark fruits and vegetables, eggs, chicken, dried fruits, wheat germ, oatmeal, spinach, and other leafy vegetables are all good sources of iron.
A shortage of iron can cause a variety of problems with your pregnancy, including anemia or premature labor in some cases.</string>
    <string name="twentyone_week_p">During week 21 of pregnancy, Mom and baby seem to be cruising right along. You are halfway through your pregnancy term and second trimester, so it is important that you continue to watch what you eat and drink as well as how you exercise at this stage.\n There are many things happening on the inside and outside of Mom’s body, but most are not yet noticeable.\n By week 21, you should have gained around fifteen pounds. You will continue to gain up to a pound of fat each week.\n As your uterus moves a ½ inch above your belly button, your abdomen is pooching out, and even strangers can tell you are pregnant now. You may begin to experience leg cramps and aches.\n To relieve the pain, try elevating your legs by using a pregnancy pillow, or even a regular pillow.
This will also help your ankles, thighs, and feet when swelling occurs. As your weight increases, you will notice that you are learning a new way to walk.\n Sometimes you may faint, so it is important you wear loose, comfortable clothes, and try wearing flat shoes instead of heels.\n Your appetite is also increasing, and although some people may advise you to increase your calorie intake by no more than 300, it is okay to eat up to 500 calories more per day at this stage.\n Just make sure you keep your doctor advised of your eating habits to ensure you are staying healthy.</string>
    <string name="twentytwo_week_p">There are many noticeable changes happening to Mom’s physical appearance during this twenty-second week of pregnancy. As you make your way past the middle of the second trimester and toward the end of it, Mom and baby are growing at a rapid, yet even pace. You are past the midway point for your pregnancy term, and most of the unpleasant pregnancy symptoms have gone away.  However, new symptoms, pregnancy pains and emotions are yet to surface, so hang in there Mom!\n The most noticeable change in this twenty-second week is going to be your weight gain. As your baby grows and your waistline expands, you can expect to gain close to a pound per week. If you weighed fifteen pounds more than at the start of your pregnancy last week and you have stayed on a healthy, well-balanced diet, chances are you have gained about a pound. Talking with your doctor about weight gain and weight loss during pregnancy is crucial, as each woman is different, and your weight will fluctuate differently during your pregnancy.\n Unfortunately, some women’s pregnancy symptoms will not have ceased and will not cease throughout the pregnancy. For most others, however, they have pretty much disappeared. Vaginal discharge is common for all women at this stage, and is due to the increase in blood flow. You are probably able to feel your baby’s movements more frequently at this point, so enjoy this twenty-second week.</string>
    <string name="twentythree_week_p">During the twenty-third week of pregnancy, both Mom and baby should be gaining weight. Mom should also be going on regular antenatal check-ups to ensure that both she and her baby are doing well and are healthy. As the second trimester comes closer to its end, these prenatal testing procedures with your healthcare practitioner are critical to keeping track of your baby’s growth and development.\n As your baby becomes more active, you’ll notice him or her kicking, hitting, or punching you more often. As your stomach muscles continue to stretch, your uterus rises about 1 ½ inches above your belly button. Depending on what your weight was last week, you may have gained up to a pound by now. The increase in blood volume in your lower part of your body will cause you to feel like you need to use the restroom more frequently. The increased amount of blood flow will also cause some women to experience vaginal discharge, although in most cases, this is normal. Continue to meet with your healthcare provider and ask any questions you may have regarding this week’s changes in your body.</string>
    <string name="twentyfour_week_p">As the 24th week of pregnancy comes and goes and you near the third trimester, it’s important to stay on top of your regular antenatal testing to check for symptoms of birth complications. Undergo a glucose test to check for gestational diabetes, which tends to occur during this time. Almost 2–5 percent of expectant moms develop this type of diabetes, so this screening is done between the 24th and 28th week of pregnancy to make sure everything is going well for both you and your baby.\n At 24 weeks some women begin to experience what is known as Braxton Hicks contractions. These are due to the tightening of the uterus that happens from time to time. You are probably showing quite a bit more, as your uterus has risen to about two inches above your belly button. As the skin continues to stretch around your abdomen and breasts, you may notice that they have become dry and itchy.\n Speaking of dryness, some women experience dry eyes at this stage; this can be relieved with over-the-counter artificial tears or drops. Always consult with your doctor first, but these drops shouldn’t be a problem. Many pregnant women will experience blurred vision during pregnancy, but it is not usually a major hindrance. As your uterus grows bigger, so do your ligaments, and some women have a hard time dealing with the round ligament pain that accompanies this process. Head cold symptoms and nasal congestion are very common among moms-to-be at this point, due to the swelling of the mucous membranes. These symptoms can be relieved with saline drops if recommended by your doctor.</string>
    <string name="twentyfive_week_p">If you haven’t yet had a glucose screening test to check for temporary gestational diabetes, you may want to consider it. Your healthcare provider has probably recommended this test, which is usually done between weeks 24–28. Don’t be surprised if a second tube of blood is taken to check for anemia and a low iron level in your system. You may also be given a TDaP vaccination for whooping cough, depending on where you live. If you are Rh negative, the time is coming soon for a Rhogam shot. This is also a good time to sign up for some birthing classes.\n As your baby’s hair grows, you’ll probably notice your own hair growing more quickly too. Try to enjoy this thicker hair because once the baby is born, chances are it will fall out. Continue to drink plenty of fluids in order to avoid dehydration, which leads to dizziness, fatigue, shortness of breath, and other pains. Don’t lie flat on your back. Hopefully you began to practice lying on your side in the early stages of your pregnancy, so even if you normally sleep on your back, the transition shouldn’t be too tough.\n Your skin may be dry and itchy from all the stretching, but lotion can help relieve the dryness. You may also notice that your eyes are dry, and they may be sensitive to light. You may experience hot flashes due to the continued increase and fluctuation in hormone levels. If you are suffering from constipation, try eating more fiber and exercising routinely to help your bowels move.
</string>
    <string name="twentysix_week_p">As you enter your twenty-sixth week of pregnancy and draw closer to the end of the second trimester, you may be feeling great one day and terrible the next. This is normal, considering the many changes happening within your body. This is also the time when you will have scheduled screening tests for anemia, gestational diabetes, and possibly a RhoGAM injection.\n By now you’ll be experiencing more frequent Braxton Hicks contractions, which feel like menstrual cramps, and you’ll frequently feel the need to use the restroom and the need to lie down. Many women begin to experience pain under their ribs as the baby kicks and stretches inside the uterus. Try changing positions to relieve the pain. You may also feel more back pain due to your increased weight — you should have gained about 20–23 pounds by this point. Try to avoid weighing yourself daily or more than once a day, as your weight will fluctuate due to water retention.


</string>
    <string name="twentyseven_week_p">The 27th week of pregnancy is a great milestone for mom and baby. It signifies the last two weeks of the second trimester and the beginning of the final phase of pregnancy. As the due date nears, this is an exciting time for the parents, grandparents, siblings, other family members, and friends. Hang in there, Mom; there are only a few more months to go!\n At 27 weeks, you may be fighting food cravings. Keep in mind that you only need 300–500 extra calories per day to remain healthy and to provide your baby with sufficient nutrients. As your uterus continues to grow and put pressure on your upper chest area, you may be experiencing chest pains or shortness of breath. This is normal, but talk to your healthcare provider about this issue if you are concerned. You may also be experiencing swelling in your face, neck, hands, feet, ankles, legs, and just about everywhere else. Try resting on your left side and relaxing as much as possible to help cope with this common pregnancy symptom.</string>
    <string name="twentyeight_week_p">As the second trimester comes to a close, the twenty-eighth week of pregnancy signifies the beginning of the end of your pregnancy. At about this time, your healthcare provider will begin showing you fetal movement charts. If your baby is in the breech position, there is still time for him or her to turn around by the due date. If your baby does not move out of the breech position, you will have to deliver via C-Section. Your blood tests will also have come back, and if your blood contains the Rh antibody, your healthcare provider will give you an anti-D injection during this week, then again in the thirty-sixth week.\n As your uterus applies pressure to your colon, constipation becomes more frequent. This is a very common symptom at this stage of pregnancy. Other symptoms such as fatigue, leg cramps, pregnancy pains, frequent urination, hemorrhoids, and insomnia continue to plague your day-to-day life. Most women also begin to experience Braxton Hicks contractions at this point; this is a false sign of labor. Some women also experience heartburn as the uterus continues to rise above the belly button and apply pressure to the stomach. The average weight gain by this week is 17 to 24 pounds, but this number is only an average, as every woman and every pregnancy is different. So keep informed, and inform your healthcare provider of any worries you may have.</string>
    <string name="twentynine_week_p">As your third trimester begins, you are definitely discovering what “pregnant” really means. You should be seeing your healthcare provider on a regular basis to ensure that you and your baby are in good health. Continue to eat right and exercise routinely to promote positive feelings about the pregnancy. To learn more about what you should be eating,  visit our Nutrition During Pregnancy page.\n As your hormones continue to fluctuate, you will experience skin rashes, dryness, and intense itching. Try to refrain from scratching your skin, and keep it moisturized. Severe skin rashes may indicate a medical problem, and should be evaluated by your physician. You may experience mood swings, and you may feel fatigued due to the amount of weight you are gaining. This is normal, as you have likely gained close to 24 pounds by this point. As you learn new ways to walk, sit, stand, and sleep, try taking warm baths to relax your muscles and help you get through some of the aches and pains. Varicose veins may begin to form on your legs, and this too is normal. Use compression stockings and elevate your feet to minimize this. You’re probably still feeling all the pregnancy symptoms you felt last week. Hang in there, Mom; only a couple of months to go!</string>
    <string name="thirty_week_p">During this thirtieth week of pregnancy and third trimester, you may feel that your pregnancy is endless. You only have a couple of more months to go, but you may be longing for your due date to come sooner. Don’t worry; you’re not alone. Most women begin experiencing these feelings as the due date approaches.\n Pregnant women gain the most weight during weeks 20 – 30. As this thirtieth week comes and goes, you will continue to gain weight, but the most dramatic physical changes are pretty much over. You may be feeling uncomfortable as you gain weight and as pregnancy pains continue to plague your daily life. Continue practicing good posture to help you gain control over your lower back pains. Pregnancy hormones will loosen up your joints and the amount of amniotic fluid will decrease as your baby grows inside you. Continue to rest and take it easy as you travel through your last trimester. This will help with all pregnancy symptoms, pains, and hormonal imbalances.</string>
    <string name="thirtyone_week_p">As you make your way through your third trimester, the biggest thing you will notice is the amount of weight you and your baby are gaining. Eating a well balanced diet (which includes foods high in fiber to help with constipation) and drinking plenty of liquids such as water or juice, is crucial in this final stage. Continue your routine checkups with your
As your baby gains weight, so do you. This thirty-first week of pregnancy signifies that birth is near, but it may feel like it’s not near enough! As your round ligament pain decreases, you may begin to experience back pain like never before. Sleeping comfortably for long periods is impossible for most expectant mothers, so try to relax and rest as much as possible in the position that is most comfortable for you. You should not sleep on your belly or flat on your back, however. A long body pillow can be very helpful to support your belly or back while you are sleeping. Your breasts begin preparing for lactation, and may begin leaking a sticky, yellowish substance called colostrum. This is perfectly normal. You may even begin leaking urine if you laugh, sneeze, or cough, and unfortunately, this too is normal. Kegel exercises may help, and wearing panty liners as a precaution is recommended.
    </string>
    <string name="thirtytwo_week_p">As you enter your eighth month of pregnancy, you are probably feeling very ready for the baby to be out of your body. Just continue to eat and exercise properly, get plenty of rest, and go to your appointments. Follow any and all instructions given to you by your healthcare provider, and don’t do anything too strenuous during these last weeks of pregnancy.\n The name of the game (as it has been) is weight gain. You should be gaining an average of a pound per week, and your blood volume has increased by up to 50 percent. You’re probably still experiencing the normal pregnancy symptoms: fatigue, leaking breasts, pregnancy pains, constipation, heartburn, insomnia, shortness of breath, cramps in your legs, vaginal discharge, nosebleeds, hemorrhoids, varicose veins, mood swings, stretch marks, contractions, and sometimes—even at this late stage—nausea. The baby may already have moved toward the pelvis in preparation for birth.</string>
    <string name="thirtythree_week_p">During your thirty-third week of pregnancy and well into your third trimester, you may be experiencing different symptoms. Your doctor may want to start seeing you more regularly from this point on, especially if you’ve had a high-risk pregnancy or complications.\n By the thirty-third week your belly should be close to the size of a  basketball. Your waistline is still growing as you gain up to one pound per week. Experts say your weight gain should be between 25 – 28 pounds, although every woman’s pregnancy varies. It can be a little more or less if your pre-pregnancy weight was higher or lower than average. You may be gaining about a pound a week, but at least half of that goes to your baby and placenta. Your doctor will have an accurate weight-gain chart available for you.


</string>
    <string name="thirtyfour_week_p">As the thirty-fourth week comes and goes, you are probably feeling much discomfort. Continue regular visits with your healthcare provider as he or she prepares you for the stages of labor. Remember that each pregnancy is different, and some women do not make it to full term (40 weeks). This is why your doctor is preparing you now. Your healthcare provider will do a vaginal culture for Group B Strep bacteria in the next few weeks. Group B Strep is a bacteria that colonizes the vagina and bowel in some women, and if untreated can cause infection in your newborn. If you are positive, your doctor will give you intravenous antibiotics during labor to decrease the amount of bacteria and likelihood of infection.\n
The biggest thing you’ll notice in this thirty-fourth week is the reduction of pressure on your chest and lungs. This is due to your baby moving down into the pelvis area. Your uterus should be close to 5 ½ inches above your belly button. Your belly button is probably extremely sensitive too, and you may notice that if it wasn’t an “outie” before, it is now. Some women have heartburn due to relaxation of the muscles in the lower esophagus. Swelling in your hands, wrists, face, legs, ankles, and feet is likely increasing. If the swelling is accompanied by severe headaches, dizziness, or pain your upper abdomen, you should contact your healthcare provider, as this could be a sign of pre-eclampsia. The swelling is due to water retention, and believe it or not, the way to reduce it is to continue drinking more water. Drinking less water only makes the situation worse.


</string>
    <string name="thirtyfive_week_p">As the thirty-fifth week of pregnancy begins, some women begin to experience anxiety about delivering their baby. This is normal, and it may help to talk with your healthcare provider. He or she may even want to begin seeing you more frequently to ensure all tests are completed and to more closely monitor your health and your baby’s. If you haven’t started Kegel exercises, now is a good time to do that. Kegels can strengthen your pelvic muscles for delivery and prepare you for the increased pressure as the baby moves into that region. It may reassure you to know that 99 percent of babies born during this week survive outside the womb.\n
You should have gained 25–29 pounds by this thirty-fifth week. Your uterus is about six inches above your belly button, and your belly button may be sensitive to the touch. People probably want to touch or rub your belly at this point, as you look very much pregnant. Your baby should be moving to a head-down position in your pelvis region, which reduces pressure on your ribs, chest, and lungs, but increases pressure on your bladder. This will cause you to urinate more often, and can become quite annoying. Back pain, pelvic pain, and pelvic numbness can all occur. The numbness is due to pressure on your pelvic nerves. This can continue until the birth of your baby. Talk to your doctor if the discomfort becomes excessive.</string>
    <string name="thirtysix_week_p">You’ve finally made it to the thirty-sixth week of your pregnancy, and now you are considered late preterm, nine months exactly from conception (full term is not until 37 weeks). Congratulations! Your baby will be born any time now, as most births take place between weeks 37–40. Although this is an exciting time, it can also be a time of anxiety. You should be seeing your doctor on a weekly basis to ensure that everything is moving along just fine. During this time all women should undergo screening for Group B Streptococcus. This bacterium is commonly found in healthy women, but if passed to the baby during birth, it can cause serious lung infections. By undergoing screening at around the 36th week, you can find out whether you carry this type of bacteria and be treated with antibiotics during labor to prevent these infections in the baby.\n Most women feel like they are “done being pregnant” by the thirty-sixth week. You are probably still suffering from fatigue, constipation, insomnia, pregnancy pains, restlessness, hemorrhoids, and everything else. Pressure in your lower abdominal area is referred to as lightening or engagement. Some women find that walking is incredibly difficult, while others have adapted to their pregnant bodies. Some women experience urinary tract infections, or UTIs, at this point. These are caused by constant trips to the restroom and hemorrhoids. There are creams to help with the hemorrhoids, but nothing can be done to reduce the frequency of urination. You may be feeling your baby resting on your pelvic bones. This is normal as he or she awaits labor and childbirth. You may also experience higher blood pressure and blood sugar levels.</string>
    <string name="thirtyseven_week_p">You’ve reached your ninth and final month, the end of your 37th week, when you are finally considered “full term.” You’ve been pregnant for most of the year, and you’re probably exhausted and ready for this baby to come out already! Try not to stress or dwell on this; your baby will be here soon enough. You may still have a few weeks to go, so try to keep your mind occupied. Your baby will be here when he or she is ready. While most babies will do well if born at 37 weeks, it is best for them to be born after 39 weeks. This is why your doctor will not induce labor or perform a cesarean delivery before that, unless medical necessity dictates otherwise.
Your caregiver may recommend a Group B strep test. Group B Strep (short for Streptococcus) is a type of bacteria that can be found in or around the area of the vagina or the rectum. It is not a problem unless your baby becomes infected as he or she comes out, in which case some serious conditions may develop. If the test is positive, however, antibiotics can be prescribed to take care of the problem.</string>
    <string name="thirtyeight_week_P">Many different changes are happening during the 38th week of pregnancy. Both Mom and baby are ready for delivery and playing a waiting game. Anxiety could be playing a major role in an expectant mom’s head, so try discussing any negative feelings you may have with your healthcare provider.\n
Believe it or not, your internal and external states are still changing. Increased mucus discharge at this stage is normal as your cervix softens and prepares for labor. As the baby moves into the birth canal many women will also experience increased pelvic pressure and back pain. Pregnancy massages and maternity belts may provide some relief for these discomforts. Swelling in your body, especially your feet, is quite apparent at this point, especially in warmer, more humid areas, as increased humidity draws fluid into the tissue. Swelling in your hands and face that is accompanied by severe abdominal pain or persistent or severe headaches should be reported to your healthcare provider immediately. This could be a sign something is wrong, such as pregnancy-induced hypertension. Pregnancy-induced hypertension can prevent the placenta from getting adequate blood, oxygen, and food to the baby.</string>
    <string name="thirtynine_week_p">If you are in your 39th week of pregnancy, get ready to celebrate; it’s almost over! You will be able to welcome your baby home soon enough. Try to enjoy these last moments of pregnancy, as motherhood is sure to bring new stresses and challenges. Your baby is utilizing most of the space inside the womb, and labor pains may begin at any moment. Continue going about your daily routine, but keep in mind that the baby can be born at any time now.\n You’re likely experiencing discomfort every moment as the 39th week comes and goes. You may be experiencing difficulty getting up from a sitting or lying position. Your breasts will continue to grow and become increasingly sensitive. You may even begin leaking a fluid called colostrum. Every part of your body is beginning to swell, but it’s important to continue drinking lots of water. If you haven’t experienced false labor contractions yet, you may begin to during this week. The easiest way to differentiate false labor contractions from real ones is that real labor contractions will prevent you from walking or talking. If your water breaks during this week, contact your healthcare provider and go immediately to the hospital. The baby is moving closer to your cervix due to a process called effacement, which means that the cervix is becoming softer, thinner, and shorter in preparation for delivery.</string>
    <string name="fourty_week_p">As you and your baby enter the 40th week, you may be quite anxious for childbirth. This can be a very happy and exciting time, but also a very challenging time for you. Again, hang in there and try to enjoy these last hours with your baby inside you. Continue preparing his or her arrival—he or she will be here soon enough (although some pregnancies go beyond the 40th week, in which case a doctor may decide to induce labor).\n Pains are increasing due to pressure caused by the amount of weight you are gaining, as well as the movements of your baby. There is now very little room for him or her to move around, so it may feel like the baby is not moving as much. Pay attention to how often he or she moves, not how strong the movements are—there’s not much room in there to wind up and give a strong kick!</string>


    <!--    //baby string&ndash;&gt;-->

    <string name="first_week_b">During the first week of pregnancy there’s no major development of the baby, other than the egg leaving the ovary and traveling to the fallopian tubes. You’re not actually pregnant at this time, since conception itself doesn’t happen until about two weeks after your period ends.\n Still, this week is included in the pregnancy calendar to help the doctor calculate the first day of your last monthly menstrual cycle. It’s from this day that the nine-month cycle (or 40 weeks in medical terms) is calculated, and your EDD (expected due date) is determined.\n Once the egg is fertilized, the cells begin to divide over the next seven to ten days. During the first week the “baby” is called a blastocyte. You can break the blastocyte into two parts — the external part of this blastocyte will become the placenta, and the internal part will be the embryo during the second week of pregnancy.If more than one egg gets released and fertilized, multiple zygotes may form. The zygotes have 46 chromosomes, an equal number from each parent, and the chromosomes have genetic material in them that determine the baby’s sex, hair color, features, skin color, height, and eye color.</string>
    <string name="second_week_b">Out of the 46 chromosomes, the two most important are the X chromosome and the Y chromosome. These two chromosomes determine the baby’s sex. Every egg has an X chromosome; every sperm has either an X or a Y chromosome.\n If the sperm fertilizes the egg with an X chromosome, you’ll have a girl. If it’s a Y chromosome, you’ll have a boy. The gender is decided at the moment of fertilization, but you won’t know until weeks later.
The baby, which at this stage is called an embryo, consists of 150 cells that will begin to divide up into three separate layers. Here’s a brief breakdown of each layer and what it eventually transforms into:\n 1st Layer: The internal layer, and also known as the endoderm or endoblast, becomes the digestive system and respiratory tract, which includes glands like the pancreas, thyroid, liver and thymus.\n 2nd Layer: The middle layer, and also known as the mesoderm, becomes the baby’s bones, cartilage, circulatory system, inner skin layer, muscles, genitalia, excretory system, and outer covering.\n
 3rd Layer: The outer layer, and also known as the ectoderm or ectoblast, becomes the nervous system, the brain, and the epidermis, which includes the baby’s skin, nails, and hair.
During this time of transformation, the embryo simply floats within the uterus, protected by the secretions of the uterus lining. The baby is still very, very small — only .1 to .2 mm long.</string>
    <string name="third_week_b">During the third week the baby is called a morula. A morula is a ball of cells that is constantly multiplying. About 30 hours after fertilization occurs, the morula begins to divide into two cells, then four, then eight and so on, as it moves from the fallopian tubes to the uterus.\n As the morula travels, it becomes known as a blastocyst, and it hollows out and fills with fluid. By the end of the week implantation occurs, meaning the blastocyst attaches to the lining of the uterus, or the endometrium.\n Once it has attached, the endometrium provides nutrients and removes waste from the embryo. Specific parts of the baby are beginning to take shape.
Features such as gender and eye, hair, and skin color have already been determined, and the brain, head, spinal cord, and gastrointestinal tract are developing.\n The heart starts beating, and the size of the baby varies from .2 mm to .5 mm.  This can be a very exciting time for new parents, as they can get their first glimpse of their new baby.</string>
    <string name="fourth_week_b">Your baby is developing very quickly during the fourth week of pregnancy. Conception, fertilization, and implantation have all occurred, and now your baby is developing into… well, a baby.\n Now called an embryo, your baby consists of two layers, called the epiblast and the hypoblast. Also, the amnion sac and yolk sac develop during this fourth week. The amnion sac fills with amniotic fluid, which protects the embryo.
The yolk sac produces the blood and helps nourish the embryo until the placenta takes over. Your baby’s vascular network is growing and helping to transport blood, oxygen, and nutrients from mother to baby by way of the umbilical cord.\n Your baby is .4 mm long — about the size of an apple seed. The heart is beating, blood is beginning to pump, and organs are developing.</string>
    <string name="fifth_week_b">By week 5 in your pregnancy, your baby is growing rapidly. By the end of the fifth week, it looks like a tadpole, tail included, and is about the size of an orange seed or 1 – 5 mm in length.
During this week, your baby’s vital organs are growing; the heart, central nervous system, bones, and muscles are forming quickly from this point on. Plus, the skeleton begins to take shape.\n Your baby’s heart is quickly developing, as it begins to separate into four chambers and starts pumping blood. Some ultrasounds will be able to pick up on the heartbeat as early as five weeks.\n The neural tube, which eventually becomes the brain and spinal cord, begins to form. The placenta develops, and through the placenta and umbilical cord, your baby receives nourishment. The eyes, ears, nose, mouth, fingers, and toes also begin to show.</string>
    <string name="sixth_week_b">At six weeks, your baby is going through visible changes. Major developments include the ears, mouth, and nose, and ultrasounds are able to pick these out quite easily. The eyes and nostrils are also forming, and they show up in an ultrasound as black dots.\n Your baby’s arms and legs look like stubs that are beginning to protrude from the body. The baby’s heartbeat is an astounding 100 – 160 beats per minute (twice as fast as yours or mine).\n The blood is circulating, and the lungs, intestines, liver, and pancreas are all forming. Your baby is approximately ¼ inch long, and resembles a lentil bean.\n At six weeks pregnant, the baby is able to make its first movements, although these movements are too gentle to be felt by the expectant mother.</string>
    <string name="seventh_week_b">Your baby is growing rapidly in the seventh week, and is close to the size of a blueberry, or up to 13mm in length. The facial features are really beginning to come into focus, as the mouth and tongue are forming.\n The eyes begin to form too, and the retina and lens have attached themselves. During this week your baby is developing its own blood type. The muscles, bones, and organs continue to grow, and the intestines and appendix are fully formed.\n The liver has begun to produce red blood cells. Your baby’s toes and fingers can be seen in an ultrasound. The teeth and the tongue are forming inside the mouth too, although they are not yet visible.</string>
    <string name="eight_week_b">The eighth week of the pregnancy calendar signifies many special things. First, the embryo is at the end of the embryonic stage and is ready to start the fetal stage. It also begins to lose the embryonic tail.\n The little bean is approximately an inch long and weighs close to three grams. As the intestines grow longer, they run out of room within the abdomen, causing them to protrude into the umbilical cord until week 12.\n Although they are hard to see, the gonads are forming into either testicles or ovaries. Ossification, or the hardening of the bones, begins to occur, and the elbows, wrists, and other bones and joints are taking shape.
Webbed feet and hands begin to grow longer and separate, and if you look closely you can almost count all twenty fingers and toes!\n The facial features are also coming into focus. The nose is clearly visible, and the ears are growing and shaping internally and externally. The jawline and mouth are also clearly visible, and the teeth are where they are supposed to be.</string>
    <string name="nineth_week_b">Your baby is now out of the embryonic period and into the fetal period. At just an inch long, your baby still weighs around three grams, about the same as during the eighth week of pregnancy.\n Most of your baby’s physical features are in place, such as the head, legs, and arms. The head is the largest of the extremities.\n During the ninth week your baby begins to put on weight. The tail that was once there should have disappeared by now, and the organs and muscles should be functioning on their own.\n His or her eyelids will fuse together, or shut, and will reopen again during the 27th week of pregnancy. Although the sex organs are developed, your doctor won’t be able to distinguish them yet.\n
That will happen during the second trimester. Your baby’s heart should also have divided into four separate chambers, and will be pumping rapidly (this is normal).</string>
    <string name="ten_week_b">You have been told up until this point that your baby is growing rapidly. Now that he or she has reached the fetal stage, however, “growing rapidly” doesn’t come close to describing what is going on. Last week, your baby was the size of a large grape.\n This week, your baby is the size of a lime. That’s quite a difference, and week-to-week from here on out, your baby will continue to grow at this rate.
As internal organs continue to grow, your baby’s vital organs—such as the kidneys, liver, intestines, and brain—start functioning on their own.\n Over the course of the next three weeks, your baby will also grow significantly larger. Details such as toenails will begin to appear, and if you look closely enough, you may be able to see peach fuzz on your baby’s skin.</string>
    <string name="eleven_week_b">Your baby is an amazing 2 ½ inches long and weighs half an ounce by this week. The head makes up half of that size, and you might imagine from looking at it that your baby is going to be a genius!\n The fingers and toes are completely separated, and you can count all 20 of them by the end of the eleventh week. The baby’s bones are hardening, but the skin is still transparent. Your baby is very active, but unfortunately he or she is still too small for Mom or anyone else to feel this activity.\n Surrounded by amniotic fluid, your baby has learned to swallow. The organs are continuing to grow and form, and some of them should already be functioning. Within the next three weeks, the baby will double in size.
More blood vessels will appear in the placenta to provide your baby with the nutrients and oxygen it needs to grow so quickly. The ears will move to the correct position, from the neck to the side of the head.</string>
    <string name="twelve_week_b">This is a very exciting week for your baby. The vocal cords form during this twelfth week, and the nails on all 20 fingers and toes become visible. The intestines are still growing, and they now have room to move into the abdomen area.\n More facial features come into focus, such as the eyebrows and lips. The brain continues to develop as it makes hormones of its own, and the nerve cells multiply rapidly. Muscles begin responding to the brain, which wants to control everything, but cannot just yet.\n As the brain and muscles develop together, natural movements such as bending of the arms, clenching and opening the fists, and twisting of the wrists and elbows become more frequent.</string>
    <string name="thirteen_week_b">As the thirteenth week of pregnancy comes and goes, many significant changes are happening to your baby. It’s almost three inches long and weighs between 0.7 and 0.8 ounces at this point.\n There is still plenty of room to grow inside the uterus, and your fetus now looks more like a baby, only extremely tiny.\n Its eyes are moving away from the sides of the head and are drawing closer to one another, and the fine hairs that make up the eyebrows are coming together. As your baby continues to grow, so does its abdomen, allowing the intestines to continue to move into their proper place.
The pancreas begins to produce insulin, which is critical for regulating sugar levels after childbirth and later in life. As the bones continue to harden, the placenta provides nutrients, vitamins, minerals, fats, proteins, and oxygen.\n The placenta also allows the transfer of blood via the bloodstream from Mom to baby. Your baby hits another milestone — it has a functional intestinal system at this point.</string>
    <string name="fourteen_week_b">Finally, your baby’s body is catching up with its rather large head. The ears and eyes continue to shift into their correct positions, as the ears move to the sides of the head and the eyes draw closer to one another.\n
As the neck grows longer, your baby’s chin lifts from its chest. The muscle reflexes continue to develop, but the baby is still too small for any of the resulting movements to be felt by Mom.\n The baby is drawing all its nutrients directly from the placenta, so again, it’s very important you watch what you put into your mouth. The baby is fully developed and is growing larger, and the system is continuing to expand.\n During an ultrasound examination, you’ll be able to see that the baby is opening and clenching its fists and spreading its fingers apart. The baby’s heart is beating twice as fast as yours, but this is normal.\n The baby is three inches long and weighs nearly an ounce by this week. Your baby will be able to suck his or her thumb at this stage, and make facial expressions like frowning and squinting.\n Plus, the liver of the baby begins to produce bile while the spleen begins to produce red blood cells.</string>
    <string name="fifteen_week_b">Your baby has grown since last week, weighing 1.75 ounces and reaching four inches in length. A fine hair called lanugo covers the skin, keeping your baby at a constant body temperature.\n The lanugo does this until the baby is born, and it disappears just before birth. During the fifteenth week, many good things are happening inside the womb.\n The biggest thing is that the bones in the ear are hardening, and your baby is now able to hear sounds, including Mom’s heartbeat, speaking, and breathing. Many future parents begin to put headphones on the belly during the second trimester, playing soft music to keep the baby calm.\n Although the baby is moving around a lot, Mom may not be able to tell just yet, although she may occasionally feel the baby kick. She may also get the occasional hiccups. These movements will be felt more easily and more often later in the pregnancy.\n Your baby is making faces, squinting and frowning, and sucking on their thumb. Since last week the arms and legs have grown longer than the head.\n This is significant, since the head has been the biggest part of the fetus until now. Taste buds are forming, and the fingernails and toenails are growing longer by the day.</string>
    <string name="sixteen_week_b">At 16 weeks old, your baby is already 4 ¾ inches long and weighs about 3.9 ounces. The facial muscles continue to develop, allowing him or her to make all kinds of different facial expressions.\n It’s important you know the reason why I keep referring to your baby as “he or she.” During this week’s ultrasound the doctor will be able to distinguish whether your baby is a boy or girl. The genitals are fully developed and can be seen with ease during the sonogram.\n As your baby continues to grow (he or she is the same size as the placenta at this point) you may be able to feel movement, which can first be noticed between 16 and 20 weeks. The development of visual sensitivity at this stage is also amazing.\n Babies have been seen protecting their eyes from bright lights with their hands at this point. Breathing on its own, he or she is able to inhale and exhale the surrounding amniotic fluid.
Your baby also begins to build fat underneath the skin, which acts as insulation. The urinary and circulatory systems are functioning and your baby is able to pump about 25 quarts of blood daily.</string>
    <string name="seventeen_week_b">At a whopping 5 ½ inches long, your baby weighs close to five ounces, more than the placenta at this stage. The umbilical cord is growing in length, strengthening and thickening. Loud noises can easily startle your baby, as their sense of hearing is developing rapidly.\n The bones are fully formed and the ears have moved into their final resting spot on the sides of the head.\n Speaking of the head, it doesn’t seem as large anymore, due to the continued growth of the arms and legs; your baby is looking more and more normal.
Adipose tissue develops and helps to regulate the body temperature, and vernix, which is a protective cover, develops over the baby’s skin.\n The little skeleton transforms from cartilage to bone, although the bones remain flexible to allow for passage through the birth canal. If your baby is a boy, he will form prostate glands during this 17th week.</string>
    <string name="eighteen_week_b">As your baby’s bones ossify, or harden, the legs are affected first. The bones in the inner ears also harden, and your baby’s hearing becomes much more acute.\n You’ll find that your baby starts to kick and react to loud sounds as the part of the brain that sends and receives nerve signals develops.
At 5 ½ inches long and weighing 5.25 ounces, your baby’s growth slows during this week, and will remain slow for several weeks to come. The baby is moving around, doing things such as crossing their legs, bending their limbs and joints, and doing somersaults.\n If you’re having a girl, during this week her uterus and fallopian tubes will form and move into the correct positions.
    </string>
    <string name="nineteen_week_b">Up until this week your baby has been measured from crown to rump, but now he or she is measured from head to toe.
At 7 ½ inches in length and weighing seven ounces, your baby has grown significantly since last week. The arms and legs are now proportional to the body, the scalp produces hair, and the skin is now covered with fine hair and a creamy material called vernix that protects it.\n The baby’s hearing is almost fully developed too. If your baby is a girl, at this point in her life her ovaries have more than 6 million eggs.\n As the bones continue to harden and the muscles become stronger, your baby becomes more active. Movements are felt more often, but the baby sleeps up to 20 hours a day.
The baby may become more active when Mom wishes to sleep, lie down, or relax. You may notice that loud noises can startle your baby during other hours.</string>
    <string name="twenty_week_b">At 11 ounces and a little more than 7 ½ inches long, your baby’s growth has slowed in recent weeks, but it will begin to accelerate again from the twentieth week forward. You’re probably feeling your baby’s movements more frequently as he or she tests the boundaries within the walls of the womb.
The lungs are not yet mature, but the baby is breathing. A dark green sticky substance called meconium is being produced. Meconium consists of cell loss and amniotic fluid that has been swallowed with digestive secretions.
Lanugo (fine hair) still covers the body, and the hair on the scalp is growing quickly. The ears are fully functioning on their own now, so it’s important to spend time in calm and quiet environments, as your baby sleeps for an average of 20 hours per day.</string>
    <string name="twentyone_week_b">21 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 133 days leftYour baby has now grown almost as big as your placenta. Your baby continues to swim around his or her warm cozy home, and his or her blood circulation is fully functional. The umbilical cord also continues to thicken and grow in length.
The digestive system keeps maturing, as the intestines begin to contract and relax on their own. The digestive system also gets practice working due to the amount of amniotic fluid your baby swallows on a regular basis.\n The eyebrows and eyelids are fully developed at this point, and the fingernails and toenails completely cover the tips of your baby’s fingers. Weighing 11 ounces and almost 8 inches in length, your baby is about the size of a large banana.22 weeks \n 2nd trimester \n 126 days left</string>

    <string name="twentytwo_week_b">At 11 inches long and weighing just under a pound, your baby is the size of a spaghetti squash during this twenty-second week. He or she is still very thin due to the lack of fatty tissues, but this will soon change. The skin is still wrinkly and covered with lanugo, but the internal organs are growing fast and the eyelids and eyebrows are becoming distinguishable. Even the eyes have formed fully, but the irises (the colored part of your eye) still lack pigment.\n The baby’s liver has started to produce the various enzymes that are required for breaking down bilirubin, a byproduct of the breaking down of red blood cells. The fetal red blood cells have a shorter lifespan, so there is more production of bilirubin in a fetus. The bilirubin from fetal blood goes into the placenta and then passes into the mother’s blood. The mother’s liver gets rid of the fetal bilirubin.\n The sensory system is also developing. Your baby learns his or her sense of touch and begins rubbing his or her face, neck, torso, and legs. If you are having a girl, the uterus, ovaries, and egg cells are fully formed</string>

    <string name="twentythree_week_b">Your baby is a little more than one pound as the twenty-third week of pregnancy comes and goes, and has reached a length of about 11.4 inches. If you look at an ultrasound, you may think your little boy or girl resembles a little doll. Your baby is forming pigmentation at this stage, and as the fat develops, the skin remains loose, since skin is produced much more quickly than fat. You may also feel kicks and punches as your baby moves within the uterine walls. This can be a very exciting time.</string>
    <string name="twentyfour_week_b">Your baby is almost a foot long and is about the same size as an ear of corn at 1 ½ pounds (approximately four ounces more than last week). The brain continues to develop, as do the taste buds and lungs. The lungs begin to develop branches and cells that produce surfactant, a chemical agent that will be needed to inflate their little air sacs once your baby is outside the womb. If a baby is born prematurely at this stage, or in weeks to come, the lack of surfactant produced during pregnancy can cause trouble breathing. With their eyes still shut, they use their hands and feet to maneuver and develop their sense of touch. The hair on the scalp is still growing at an even pace, and your baby is continuing to inhale amniotic fluid into its lungs as practice for breathing after birth.</string>
    <string name="twentyfive_week_b">At an amazing 13½ inches long and weighing just over 1½ pounds, your baby is growing rapidly. During week 25, your baby starts to plump up as fat builds up under the skin. If you were to have a 3-D ultrasound, your baby would finally start to look more like a person, and less like a miniature skeleton! At this stage, most patients report feeling a LOT of fetal movement. Do not worry, lots of movement is a good thing, and no, this is not a sign that your baby is going to be hyperactive.</string>
    <string name="twentysix_week_b">Your baby is growing quite gradually at this point, weighing about two pounds and close to 14 inches in length. During the twenty-sixth week your baby’s eyelids (which have been sealed shut until now) begin to open and blink on their own. The eyes are blue, but this will often change after birth. The development of your baby’s eyes is almost complete, and although he or she still seems very lean, fat is definitely building underneath the skin and will continue to do so until birth. The fetal heart is pumping blood, the lungs are developing blood vessels, and the circulatory system is fully functional. The umbilical cord continues to grow stronger and thicker and provides your baby with all essential nutrients. If you are having a boy, the testicles will move into the scrotum during this week.</string>
    <string name="twentyseven_week_b">As the end of the second trimester arrives, your baby should be close to 15 inches in length and weigh over two pounds. As the eyes continue to develop, the layers of the retina are forming, and the membrane that covers the eyes separates to form eyelids. You may notice that your baby is developing its own waking and sleeping patterns. This is normal, and many doctors suggest you try to rest as much as possible while the baby is resting. The tissues and grooves in your baby’s brain continue to form. Some experts believe that the baby begins to dream at this point, but there is no conclusive proof that this is happening. You may also feel your baby hiccuping as their lungs continue to mature and they inhale and exhale amniotic fluid.</string>
    <string name="twentyeight_week_b">At 16 inches long and weighing close to four pounds, your baby is continuing to grow at a steady pace. For the last few weeks, the growth has seemed to slow down, but from this week on your baby’s growth will start to pick up speed again. You may notice in the ultrasound images that he or she is looking plump. This is due to the fat that continues to build under the skin. The eyes have opened, and the eyebrows and eyelids are fully formed, and even the eyelashes are now visible. The enzyme system and the endocrinological processes are still developing, and the lungs are still maturing as the third trimester begins. As your baby moves around, you may be feeling kicks and punches more frequently.</string>
    <string name="twentynine_week_b">During the twenty-ninth week, your baby’s kicks and punches may be so hard that they take your breath away, and they may cause severe pain. The movements and kicks are happening frequently at this point, which are goods signs that the baby is doing well.  Sometimes these kicks and movements can cause rib pain, pelvic pain, and unintentional loss of urine. This high activity does not usually last throughout the pregnancy and will become less frequent as the baby grows and has more limited space to move around.\n Your baby is continuing to grow, weighing close to three pounds and stretching to over a foot long. You may notice that this growth is causing increased hunger, as your baby uses most of the nutrients you consume to grow more. You may feel like you need to eat again after a meal, but fight this temptation and trust that your baby is receiving all the nutrients it needs. Rapid brain development began last week and continues this week. The muscles and lungs continue to mature, and hearing has improved greatly.
    </string>
    <string name="thirty_week_b">Your baby would have quite a wrinkled appearance if you could see it. But as the fat tissue builds, the wrinkles in your baby’s skin will start to smooth out. Fine hair called lanugo still covers your baby’s body, and will remain there until birth. At about 17 inches and weighing around four pounds, your baby is practicing breathing on its own by repeatedly moving its diaphragm in preparation for life outside the womb. Because of this practicing, you may feel flutters within your uterus when your baby has the hiccups. The baby is also getting into his or her own sleeping and waking routine, and becoming more active while awake. Your baby has grown so much that it takes up almost the entire uterine cavity. As the brain continues to mature, it begins to train the eyes, muscles, and lungs to function on their own. The digestive tract is fully functional at this thirtieth week, as your baby continues to take nutrients from you and process them.</string>

    <string name="thirtyone_week_b">At 15 inches and weighing between three and three and one-half pounds , your baby is over half the size he or she will be at birth. As baby fat continues to accumulate, your baby will gain weight much more quickly in these last two months. The digestive tract and lungs are almost mature, and the lungs are able to inflate properly at this point, producing surfactant to help prevent the collapse of the lungs after birth. The ears are fully developed, and your baby is listening to everything it can hear inside the womb. Babies at this stage can hear Mom’s breathing  and heartbeat, they can hear music, and they can hear the voices of others. At this stage, very loud noises or events such as a rock concerts should be avoided!
The toenails and fingernails are fully formed, and the baby can even scratch itself in the womb. Amniotic fluid is extremely important at this point. Your baby is swallowing and urinating up to a half liter a day. If there’s too much amniotic fluid in the sac, it could mean your baby isn’t swallowing properly and could have gastrointestinal problems. If there is too little amniotic fluid, it could mean your baby isn’t urinating properly and could have kidney problems, or perhaps a placenta problem.\n Your OB doctor should be using a measuring tape or ultrasound to assess the size of your belly or directly estimate the size of your baby. The size of your belly helps the doctor determine if there is a problem. If there is a discrepancy between the size of your belly and the stage you have reached in your pregnancy, your doctor may order an ultrasound to see what is going on.</string>
    <string name="thirtytwo_week_b">You may notice that your baby seems much calmer these days. This is mainly due to the fact that there’s less room inside the womb. Most babies have their head down, whereas others have completely turned around and put themselves into the breech position. The majority will turn back to a head-down presentation. If your baby hasn’t yet, it’s okay; it’ll happen sometime before birth. If not, then your child may need to be delivered via C-section.\n Your baby has grown to 16–17 inches long and weighs about 4 ½ pounds by this thirty-second week. The baby is sleeping in segments of 20–40 minutes at a time, and you may be distressed that your normal sleeping patterns have been disrupted. Hang in there; this is normal. Studies show that some babies dream at this stage.\n The brain is continuing to develop, so eating properly is still very important. The umbilical cord is coated with a gelatinous substance to protect it from kinks and knots when the baby turns and twists. The baby’s skeleton is completely formed by now, but the bones are still soft and flexible.</string>
    <string name="thirtythree_week_b">Your baby should weigh between 4 ½ and 5 pounds by this thirty-third week, and be almost 17 inches in length. As the fatty layers continue to build under the skin, all the bones (except for the skull) continue to harden. The reason the skull doesn’t harden is that it needs to remain flexible and soft in order to travel through the birthing canal. In addition, the sutures between the bones of the skull are not completely closed, which allows for some “play” during birth.
Your baby should be in a head-down position by this time, but if not, there is no need to worry, as there is still plenty of time left. Some people say yoga exercises can help your baby to move into the correct position, but consult with your healthcare provider before beginning any new activities in the third trimester. As the lungs continue to mature, your baby is continuing to practice his or her breathing patterns for life outside the womb. You may notice that your baby is sleeping more often (though still not enough to let you relax), and those kicks, turns, and punches are a bit more painful. This is due to your baby’s growth — he or she isn’t moving any more than in earlier weeks, there’s just a little less room now.</string>
    <string name="thirtyfour_week_b">As your baby continues to grow in length and weight, he or she should weigh close to five pounds and measure between 15 ½ and 17 ½ inches. Most of the organs are almost fully matured, with the exception of the lungs. The facial features are very distinct at this point. As the fat continues to build under the skin, your baby is looking a bit plumper and is taking on his or her mature facial characteristics. He or she will continue to grow as the due date approaches. You may notice too that he or she is still getting the hiccups. This is normal.</string>
    <string name="thirtyfive_week_b">Your baby has reached an amazing 18 inches and weighs approximately six pounds by this point. Even though most of the development is complete, your baby will continue to plump up and put on weight. His or her liver is functioning and producing waste on its own, and the kidneys are also fully matured. You will continue to feel kicks as the space inside the amniotic sac continues to shrink. The baby’s ears are fully formed and functioning just fine, so talk to him or her as often as possible. The lanugo begins to disappear, but fine vellus hair begins to grow to replace it.</string>
    <string name="thirtysix_week_b">At the thirty-sixth week, your baby has pretty much finished growing, although he or she will continue to build fat under the skin, causing the arms, legs, knees, cheeks, and face to plump more and more. He or she is one week away from being considered full term, at 19 inches in length and weighing around six pounds.</string>
    <string name="thirtyseven_week_b">Your baby is growing at a much slower rate these days, about ½ ounce per day. Before, his or her skin was very loose and wrinkly. These days it’s becoming much smoother due to the fat building up under the skin. His or her lungs are well developed, and breathing movements are more frequent as the baby gets the hang of the inhale/exhale process. The amniotic fluid continues to decrease as your baby grows, and he or she weighs approximately 6½ to 7 pounds and is about 19 inches long by now. The baby’s hair has been growing rapidly, and depending on genetics he or she could have a full head of hair at this point.</string>
    <string name="thirtyeight_week_b">Your baby should be in position with his or her head on your pelvic bone. The lanugo is continuing to shed as this week comes and goes. If you haven’t given birth, your baby is continuing to grow. He or she could be up to 20 inches in length (normally they are between 17–20 inches by this week) and weighing close to or just over seven pounds. All your baby’s organs have matured and are functioning on their own.\n A major development during this 38th week is that the tear ducts begin to form. The gender can easily be identified now, as the sex organs have fully matured. Expectant parents who do not wish to know the gender of the baby before childbirth will definitely need to resist looking at the ultrasounds now. Your baby is reacting to sounds, clenching his or her fists, and preparing for childbirth. It is said that girls are smaller than boys and rest lower in the abdomen, but every pregnancy is unique.</string>
    <string name="thirtynine_week_b">If your baby is born during this week, he or she will likely be healthy, and all organs will be able to function on their own. The lungs are mature by the 39th week, but they won’t function on their own until after birth. Your baby could weigh as much as seven pounds—or even a little more—if you give birth during this week. If you do not give birth this week, however, your baby will continue to grow. He or she should remain active until birth, so if there is a decrease in movement at this stage, contact your healthcare provider.</string>
    <string name="fourty_week_b">Your baby is pretty much done developing by this last week of pregnancy, and is waiting for its arrival in the new world. All internal organs are functioning, although the lungs and brain will continue to form and develop even after birth.Your baby is now developing immunities that will be needed for survival after birth. At this point, if you have not given birth, your baby can weigh up to ten pounds and may be as long as 21 inches. All of his or her bones have hardened except for the skull, which remains soft for delivery. As he or she continues to move around in a small space, your pains may increase. Hang in there, Mom!</string>


    <string name="note">Note</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="Pregnancy">Pregnancy</string>
    <string name="babydimentions">Baby dimentions:</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="length">Length</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="Sizeof">Size of</string>
    <string name="today">today</string>
    <string name="week">week</string>
    <string name="month">month</string>
    <string name="expected">expected</string>
    <string name="Personalization">Personalization</string>


    <string name="Feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="Notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="SelectLanguage"> Select Language</string>
    <string name="Sendfeedback">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="RateUs">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="Lastperiod">Last period</string>
    <string name="Duedate">Due date</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="checked">Checked</string>


    <string name="babyshoptitle1">babyshoptitle1</string>
    <string name="babyshoptitle2">babyshoptitle2</string>
    <string name="babyshoptitle3">babyshoptitle3</string>
    <string name="babyshoptitle4">babyshoptitle4</string>


    <string name="babyshopdes1">babyshopdes1</string>
    <string name="babyshopdes2">babyshopdes1</string>
    <string name="babyshopdes3">babyshopdes1</string>
    <string name="babyshopdes4">babyshopdes1</string>


    <string name="womenshoptitle1">womenshoptitle1</string>
    <string name="womenshoptitle2">womenshoptitle2</string>
    <string name="womenshoptitle3">womenshoptitle3</string>
    <string name="womenshoptitle4">womenshoptitle4</string>


    <string name="womenshopdes1">womenshopdes1</string>
    <string name="womenshopdes2">womenshopdes2</string>
    <string name="womenshopdes3">womenshopdes3</string>
    <string name="womenshopdes4">womenshopdes4</string>

    <string name="Selectedweek">Selected week 1/40</string>

    <!-- AdMob ad unit IDs -->
    <string name="banner_home_footer">ca-app-pub-0664570763252260/3326522424</string>
    <string name="interstitial_full_screen">ca-app-pub-0664570763252260/1769900428</string>


</resources>
